- Hello.
- Hi.
- 你好。- 你好。
We’re going to Taipei.
我们要去台北。
Yes.
是的。
We’re having our first fan meeting In Taipei.
我们要举行我们在台北的第一次粉丝见面会
I’m excited.
我很兴奋。
I feel excited every time we have a fan meeting, no matter how many we have done it.
每次有粉丝见面会时，我都会感到兴奋，无论我们已经举办过多少次。
Although we have practiced, performing in front of a large group of fans is unnerving.
尽管我们已经练习过，但在一大群粉丝面前表演还是会让人感到紧张。
I am nervous but I try to stay focused.
我很紧张，但我尽量保持专注。
If P’Milk is nervous, I need to stay composed.
如果 P’Milk 感到紧张，我需要保持冷静。
If I’m nervous, she needs to stay composed.
如果我紧张，她需要保持冷静。
Alternately.
交替着来
See you in Taipei.
在台北见啦
I’m ready.
我准备好了。
We are getting better from the last time.
我们比上次变得更好了
I feel less nervous.
我感觉不那么紧张了。
♪ When you get butterflies, while you’re by my side ♪
♪ 当你在我身边感到心跳加速  ♪
♪ Just blush for me if you don’t mind ♪
♪ 如果你不介意的话，请为我脸红吧 ♪
This is my first time in Taipei. I received such a warm welcome.
这是我第一次来台北。我受到了非常热烈的欢迎。
I’m very excited. This is my first time here. Many MuvMuv came to see us.
我非常兴奋。这是我第一次来这里。许多 MuvMuv 来见我们。
Are you excited to see us?
你来看我们的时候兴奋吗？
That’s a wrap for our fan meeting in Taipei.
台北的粉丝见面会结束了。
When we arrived at the airport, many fans came to welcome us.
到达机场时，许多粉丝前来迎接我们。
It was very sweet.
这非常暖心。
Many fans also arrived at the venue early.
许多粉丝也提前到达了现场。
We had a rehearsal earlier this morning.
今天早上我们进行了彩排。
They woke up early to meet us.
她们为了见我们早早地起来了
I feel the same way as Love.
我的感觉和 Love 一样。
I got a glimpse of the special project our fans prepared for us.
我看到了粉丝们为我们准备的很特别的应援企划。
Really?
真的吗？
Oh, right. It’s in front of the hall.
噢，是的。在大厅前面。
It’s very sweet.
这非常甜蜜。
I also want to thank our fans at home who send us a lot of support online.
我还要感谢在家里通过网络给于我们大量支持的粉丝们。
You can send us support from afar. Thank you so much.
你们可以从远程给我们提供支持。非常感谢。
Even though you can’t be here, it’s okay.
尽管你们不能在现场，但是没关系。
We see the support you sent to us. We read your posts on the hashtags.
我们看到了你们送来的支持。我们阅读了你们在标签上的帖子。
Thank you for the support from the fans here and those who are at home.
感谢在现场和在家里的粉丝们的支持。
Let’s see where we will hold our fan meeting next.
让我们看看下次粉丝见面会会在哪里举行吧。
That’s right. Please stay tuned.
没错，请持续关注。
Bye.
再见。